[{"id":1,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"Top of the Elvey Building at the University of Alaska Fairbanks","bounds":"-147.85044729709625,64.85925701299541,-147.84871995449066,64.8597139560051","created_at":"2013-11-23T20:24:12.272Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T20:38:40.783Z"},{"id":2,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"The entrance to Fort Wainwright","bounds":"-147.7111279964447,64.83251232901021,-147.69567847251892,64.83617129103229","created_at":"2013-11-23T20:47:27.707Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T21:02:08.302Z"},{"id":3,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"Diomede Island Airport on Little Diomede","bounds":"-168.96615386009216,65.75527016057886,-168.93868803977966,65.76118184603028","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:00:49.750Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:00:49.750Z"},{"id":4,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"UAF Campus circle of sculptures outside the Great Hall and Rasmuson Library","bounds":"-147.82299220561978,64.85674710650986,-147.81955897808075,64.85751178387851","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:06:17.630Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:06:17.630Z"},{"id":5,"name":null,"question":"What airport is this?","answer":"Ted Stevens Anchorage International Airport (ANC)","bounds":"-150.10336875915527,61.15048357424318,-149.88364219665527,61.2100637589704","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:13:37.647Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:13:37.647Z"},{"id":6,"name":null,"question":"What airport is this?","answer":"Deadhorse Airport","bounds":"-148.57378005981445,70.17870083946805,-148.35405349731445,70.22056828269668","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:16:02.589Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:16:02.589Z"},{"id":7,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"Fort Yukon","bounds":"-145.29925346374512,66.55734798691051,-145.18939018249512,66.5819210225759","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:17:31.112Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:17:31.112Z"},{"id":8,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"Delta Junction","bounds":"-145.6790542602539,63.963606338080446,-145.2396011352539,64.07189934940193","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:23:50.047Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:23:50.047Z"},{"id":9,"name":null,"question":"Where and What is this?","answer":"This is near Kodiak and is a \u003Ca href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LORAN\" target=\"_blank\"\u003ELoran navigation site\u003C/a\u003E","bounds":"-152.35350608825684,57.77125631610757,-152.32604026794434,57.77949461870499","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:26:40.155Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:27:36.622Z"},{"id":10,"name":null,"question":"What is this?","answer":"UAF Botanical Gardens","bounds":"-147.86188155412674,64.8558502068361,-147.85844832658768,64.85667075153985","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:36:51.201Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:36:51.201Z"},{"id":11,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"Nome, Alaska","bounds":"-165.47912120819092,64.49089338103508,-165.36925792694092,64.5174940619532","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:38:52.818Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:38:52.818Z"},{"id":12,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"This is the Homer spit","bounds":"-151.53691291809082,59.60509097944164,-151.41331672668457,59.63990110935263","created_at":"2013-11-23T22:49:49.254Z","updated_at":"2013-11-23T22:50:04.375Z"},{"id":13,"name":null,"question":"Where is this?","answer":"Pioneer Park","bounds":"-147.77798473834991,64.83816708623317,-147.77025997638702,64.83999624511306","created_at":"2013-11-24T00:06:23.896Z","updated_at":"2013-11-24T00:06:23.896Z"}]